

## **Career Objective**

Seeking the role in Marketing Industry to utilize my 2.5 years social media, email marketing, content development, and PPC Marketing experience in identifying trends, engaging users and increasing brand awareness through unique and innovative marketing strategies and campaigns.

### **Education**

2021-23 | PGDM (Pursuing)
GIBS Business School, Bangalore

2018 | B.COM | 75%

Alexia College of Professional Studies, Indore

2015 | 12TH STANDARD | 88%

Central India Academy

2013 | 10TH STANDARD | 7.4 CGPA Central India Academy

#### **Contact**

C

+91-9691285008

 $\geq \sim$ 

sameersaini765@gmail.com

in

www.linkedin.com/in/-sameer-saini-ss

## Hobbies

- Sports
- Photography
- Travelling
- Music

#### **Personality**

- Team Player
- Adaptable
- Interpersonal Skills
- Inquisitive
- High Emotional Intelligence

# **Work Experience**

Seize The Ads | Indore | March 2018

Social Media Intern

Seize The Ads | Indore | April 2018 - Sept 2020 (2.5 years)

Digital Marketing Manager

Ampexcel Technologies | Noida(U.P) | Sept 2022-Oct 2022

Social Media Intern

#### **Skills**

- Wordpress
- Basic MS-Excel
- Social Media Platforms
- Basic Graphic Designing
- AdWords, Facebook Paid Ads
- · Email Marketing
- PPC Marketing
- Content Development

#### Certifications

MASTERS DIPLOMA IN DIGITAL MARKETING

Digital Gurukul | Indore | Jan 2018 - April 2018

DIGITAL MARKETING

Google Certification | April 2018

**ICAI** 

Orientation Course | September 2017

ICAI

Information Technology Training | OCtober 2017

#### **Projects**

INNOVATION | RESEARCH | ENTREPRENEURSHIP PROJECT

Silver Medalist in the IRE Project

**BUSINESS MASTERY PROGRAMME** 

Vendor management, product sales, customer engagement and marketing.

SOCIAL INTERNSHIP PROJECT

Worked on Project 'Paryavaran' for SpeakUp World Foundation

# Achievements

- Executive Member of IRE Society
- Led Photography team in National Level Management Fest "Enchainer 2k22"
- Participation in Photography Event of National Level Management Fest "Perception 2k22" by M.S Ramaiah University
- Participation in Photography Event of National Level Cultural Fest " Element7" by Krupanidhi College

### Languages

- English
- Hindi